<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RIT Linux Wiki</title>
    <link>https://moralcode.github.io/rit-linux-wiki/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RIT Linux Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0</copyright><atom:link href="https://moralcode.github.io/rit-linux-wiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connecting to the RIT eduroam network under Linux</title>
      <link>https://moralcode.github.io/rit-linux-wiki/network/rit-wifi-eduroam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moralcode.github.io/rit-linux-wiki/network/rit-wifi-eduroam/</guid>
      <description>Getting the config  Create a temporary directory somewhere and cd into it from a terminal download the linux installer from https://rit.edu/wifi. Dont open it since it might break the CRLF line endings and the binary file thats encoded at the bottom of the file if you save it after opening on a linux machine. run sed -e &#39;0,/^#ARCHIVE#$/d&#39; &amp;quot;PATH_TO_INSTALLER.run&amp;quot; | gzip -d | tar -x inside that folder to extract the contents create a new python file in that folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting to the RIT VPN under Linux</title>
      <link>https://moralcode.github.io/rit-linux-wiki/network/rit-vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moralcode.github.io/rit-linux-wiki/network/rit-vpn/</guid>
      <description>Using Network-manager These instructions are for network-manager specifically, but should be adaptable for any system
Step 1: Navigate to https://vpn.rit.edu from a linux device and sign in
Step 2: Click the button to download the anyconnect client for linux. You should get a roughly 5-6 megabyte .sh script file.
Step 3: Extract This installer script contains an encoded tarball which makes up the bulk of the file. To extract it, use this script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Design Majors</title>
      <link>https://moralcode.github.io/rit-linux-wiki/majors/gdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moralcode.github.io/rit-linux-wiki/majors/gdd/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot more you can do with linux than you might imagine.
 Unreal Engine 4 can be used on Linux and will export Linux-native builds of your games (Unity and CryEngine can also export this way) Godot is a completely FOSS engine which is sorta the Linux gamedev engine right now. Sites like GOG and Steam support Linux very well, there&amp;rsquo;s really no reason not to Linux users are often willing to help contribute back and debug software  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
